<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-09-05T18:58:53+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Canard Presse</title><subtitle>Restaurant reviews</subtitle><entry><title type="html">YuMe Sushi Deventer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/05/yume-sushi-deventer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="YuMe Sushi Deventer" /><published>2018-09-05T18:53:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-09-05T18:53:20+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/09/05/yume-sushi-deventer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/05/yume-sushi-deventer.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday evening we decided to go out grab some sushi at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yumesushi.nl/deventer/&quot;&gt;Yume Sushi Deventer&lt;/a&gt; Boreelplein 52.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;table--service-&quot;&gt;Table ✔ Service 💨&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had no reservations and we just walked in. The lady at the counter walked us to our table and left us with nothing, no food, no drink, not even an activation code for the tablet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those that never have been to YuMe they work with a tablet, it needs to be activated to be able to order a drink, Sushi or even to call for assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After about 10 minutes my husband got the attention of the waiters and he asked her to activate the tablet. She left and we had to wait another 5 minutes without knowing what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to leave when another waiter came to activate the tablet. She asked us if we made reservations. This sounded a bit strange in our ears and Hans stood up and was ready to leave, but this waitress kept very calmly and friendly so we decided to stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;food&quot;&gt;Food&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sushi was nice, not too big, not too small, a bit too much sauce and we saw some basic tricks that they do to get people to drink and eat less but that is a story for a different time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JMxIxsklaQZd2IumcTJYuNfnX6m2GwC2qEivk_j6lNdlawSgZ4WlZ-KClQxlIAbsfH_D7pVDrxs&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot; title=&quot;YuMe Sushi, Not too big, Not Too small, Bit too much sauce&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Angela Kruse&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday evening we decided to go out grab some sushi at Yume Sushi Deventer Boreelplein 52.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Food is love, Food is passion but a evening at a restaurant will cost you quickly a week of groceries for a small family</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/05/introduction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Food is love, Food is passion but a evening at a restaurant will cost you quickly a week of groceries for a small family" /><published>2018-09-05T18:51:26+02:00</published><updated>2018-09-05T18:51:26+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/09/05/introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/05/introduction.html">&lt;p&gt;We are &lt;strong&gt;Hans and Angela Kruse&lt;/strong&gt; and we are here to share our passion for most likely restaurant food. Telling our story about what we’ve seen. Not only about the food but also about the entire experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A little disclaimer seems to be nessersarry. We are not professionals, just food lovers (We are level 6 and 8 at Google local guide). It’s just our experience, our oppinion in that moment, this does not mean that you will experience the same thing or that a restaurant can’t improve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope that you would like to go on this journey with us. 
we would also love hearing your story.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are Hans and Angela Kruse and we are here to share our passion for most likely restaurant food. Telling our story about what we’ve seen. Not only about the food but also about the entire experience.</summary></entry></feed>